A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 2000-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Constituent Correspondence, 2002-2006., Extent: 10.7 cu. ft. (Box 7-37)
  - #2309506 - 2310861, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - #2311022 - 2315741, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - #2316625 - 2319669, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - #2319887 - 2324008, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - #2324921 - 2327338, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - #2327687 - 2336499, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - #2334329 - 2336874, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - #2336879 - 2339536, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - #2339540 - 2341913, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - #2341915 - 2343563, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - #2345643 - 2348154, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - #2348520 - 2350265, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - #2350501 - 2355631, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - #2355967 - 2359031, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - #2359035 - 2359719, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - #2359751 - 2362278, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - #2363317 - 2367457, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - #2368798 - 2365186, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - #2365241 - 2368545, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - #2369412 - 2371771, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - #2371854 - 2376946, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - #2377257 - 2382732, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - #2383144 - 2386119, 2004. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - #2386188 - 2388366, 2004-2005. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - #2388871 - 2393958, 2004-2005. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - #2393898 - 2394831, 2005. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - #2395017 - 2400776, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - #2400787 - 2401740, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - #2401745 - 2404003, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - #2404113 - 2408014, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - #2408444 - 2413289, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - #2413187 - 2417653, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - #2417714 - 2423398, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - #2423676 - 2427200, 2005. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - #2427335 - 2431742, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - #2431762 - 2436339, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - #2436347 - 2439038, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - #2439180 - 2440621, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - #2441005 - 2444889, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - #2445344 - 2448656, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - #2451331 - 2454307, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - #2454432 - 2455183, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - #2455217 - 2457956, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - #2458115 - 2461964, 2005. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - #2462380 - 2467614, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - #2467697 - 2472010, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - #2472335 - 2479972, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - #2481147 - 2484149, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - #2484607 - 2489758, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - #2489818 - 2494392, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - #2494802 - 2497047, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - #2497117 - 2499981, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - #2500121 - 2505776, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - #2505787 - 2510106, 2005. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - #2510205 - 2512635, 2005. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - #2512642 - 2559079, 2005. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - #2559082 - 2559703, 2005. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - #2559736 - 2564060, 2005-2006. (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Series IV. Decision Briefs, 2002-2005., Extent: .53 cu. ft. (Box 38-39)
  Contains decision briefs sent to the Governor that were prepared by agencies under the heading of the Secretary of Public Safety, as well as many briefs prepared by outside agencies that would potentially affect agencies under the Public Safety heading. All of the briefs contain a request, a recommendation, evidence of agency head concurrence, and approval or disapproval by the Governor. The decision briefs are often in the form of packets that contain additional supporting documentation and email communication. Notable topics include budgetary matters, disaster assistance and planning, and agency consolidation.
  The decision briefs are arranged chronologically by the date of submission by the requesting agency.
  - Decision Briefs, 2002 May-August. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Decision Briefs, 2002 August. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Decision Briefs, 2002 August. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Decision Briefs, 2002 October-December. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Decision Briefs, 2003 January-May. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Decision Briefs, 2003 June-November. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Decision Briefs, 2004 April-August. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Decision Briefs, 2004 August. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Decision Briefs, 2004 August. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Decision Briefs, 2004 September. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Decision Briefs, 2004 October-December. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Decision Briefs, 2005 January-July. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Decision Briefs, 2005 August-December. (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Series V. Federal Grants, 2002-2005., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (Box 40)
  Contains material pertaining to federal grant money allocated to agencies under the heading of the Secretary of Public Safety. The various branches of the Department of Criminal Justice Services received many of the grants. This series includes information on funding under the Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention Act (2002), the State Incentive Enhancement Grant (SIG) (2003), and the Virginia Services, Training, Officers, Prosecution (V-STOP) Violence Against Women grant program (2003). Also included is information on the funding of programs under the Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act (2004 and 2005), the State Homeland Security Grant program (2004), the Justice Assistance Grant (JAG) program (2005), and the Law Enforcement Terrorism Prevention Program (LETPP) (2005).
  The files are arranged chronologically.
  - Federal Grants, 2002 March. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Federal Grants, 2002 March. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Federal Grants, 2002 December. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Federal Grants, 2003 January-February. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Federal Grants, 2003 April-June. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Federal Grants, 2003 July. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Federal Grants, 2004. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Federal Grants, 2005 February-August. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Federal Grants, 2005 September. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Federal Grants, 2005 September. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Federal Grants, 2005 September. (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Series VI. Historical Records, 2002-2005., Extent: 3.6 cu. ft. (Box 41-50)
  Contains material pertaining to various public safety issues that garnered attention during the Warner Administration. The files contain correspondence (constituent and internal), reports, press material, notes, and other working papers associated with each topic. Topics include: Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) privatization, the Amber Alert system, the murder of convicted sex offender Richard A. Ausley, the Bias-Based Policing Advisory Panel (racial profiling), the Corrections Facility Task Force (prison closings), the DUI Task Force, gang activity, hurricanes and storms (such as Isabel and Gaston), narcotics enforcement, the Washington D.C. area sniper attacks, and the Virginia Citizen Soldier Support Council. The records served as subject files compiled by the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety for reference purposes. The records contain an abundance of behind-the-scenes commentary on some of the biggest issues of Governor Warner's term. The two largest categories are the files pertaining to the Bias-Based Policing Advisory Panel and the Corrections Facility Task Force.
  The topics are arranged alphabetically, as are the folder titles within each category. The type of arrangement varies within each folder, but is usually chronological. The majority of the historical records are comprised of various types of correspondence. In most cases, constituent and internal correspondence are mixed together, and arranged chronologically. However, in some cases they are arranged differently. For example, the correspondence for the Corrections Facility Task Force that was submitted directly to the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety is labeled "loose," and is arranged chronologically. The letters submitted to the Governor's Office that were rerouted to the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety are filed according to their outgoing system number. The internal correspondence folders are arranged chronologically, and contain email messages, letters, and memos sent between employees of the Secretary of Public Safety. Additionally, an introductory video for members of the Biased-Based Policing Advisory Panel is boxed separately from the paper files in box 51. Researchers interested in correspondence should also utilize the Agency Correspondence and Constituent Correspondence series.
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Privatization, 2002-2003.
    - Briefing on ABC Privatization, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2003. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - House Bill No. 1985, 2003. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Press Material, 2003. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Report- "Privatization of Virginia's Alcoholic Beverage Sales: A Preliminary Feasibility Study," 2003. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Amber Alert System, 2002-2005.
    - Correspondence, 2002-2005. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Plans and Policies, 2002-2005 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Ausley, Richard A., 2004.
    - Correspondence, 2004 February-June. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 2004 June-August. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Press Material, 2004. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Bias-Based Policing Advisory Panel (Racial Profiling), 2002-2005.
    - Committee Membership Lists, 2003; undated. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2003. (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Draft Reports, 2002-2003. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Draft Reports, 2003. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Draft Reports, 2003. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Draft Reports, 2004. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - The Governor's Biased Policing Advisory Panel background information, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - The Governor's Biased Policing Advisory Panel background information, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - The Governor's Biased Policing Advisory Panel background information, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - The Governor's Biased Policing Advisory Panel background information, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - The Governor's Preventing Crime in Virginia's Minority Communities Task Force Report, 2005. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Meeting Information, 2002-2003. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Press Conference-Announcement on Bias-Based Policing Initiatives, 2003. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Press Material, 2003-2005. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Report-"Bias-Based Policing: A Study for The Commonwealth of Virginia," 2004. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Report-"Bias-Based Policing: A Study for The Commonwealth of Virginia," 2004. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Report-"Bias-Based Policing: A Study for The Commonwealth of Virginia," 2004. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Report of the Governor's Advisory Panel on Biased-Based Policing, 2003. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Report-"Racial Profiling in Virginia: An Analysis of State and Local Law" (copy 1), 2002. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Report-"Racial Profiling in Virginia: An Analysis of State and Local Law" (copy 2), 2002. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Video Cassette- Introduction for Biased-Based Policing Advisory Panel Members, undated. (Box 51)
  - Corrections Facility Task Force (Prison Closings), 2002-2004.
    - Assessment of Facility Closing Proposal, 2002. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Brunswick Correctional Center Petition, 2002. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Brunswick Correctional Center Informational Guide, undated. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2036291-2037613), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2037618-2038268), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2038269-2038591), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2038593-2038823), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2038824-2039184), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2039185-2039320), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2039323-2039467), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2039607-2039912), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2039932-2040175), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2040208-2040422), 2002. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2040423-2041461), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2041576-2042576), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2042579-2043232), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2043250-2044169), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2044170-2044702), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2044706-2047460), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2047463-2047885), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Constituent Correspondence (#2047889-2052453), 2002. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 August 2-9. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 August 9. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 August 9-13. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 August 14-18. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 August 19-23. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 August 24-30. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 September 1-5. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 September 6-10. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence (loose), 2002 September 11-October 1. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Corrections Facility Task Force Report, 2002. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Economic Impact Material, 2002-2004. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Internal Correspondence, 2002 April 22-August 6. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Internal Correspondence, 2002 August 7-23. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Internal Correspondence, 2002 August 25-October 1. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Offender Risk Assessment Evaluation, undated. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Out-of-State Inmate Information, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Plan for the Closure of Staunton Correctional Center, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Press Material, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Southampton Correctional Center Petition, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Southampton Correctional Center Petition, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Southampton Correctional Center Petition, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Southampton Correctional Center Petitions, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Task Force Meeting Information, 2002 August 7. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Task Force Meeting Information, 2002 August 29. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Task Force Meeting Information, 2002 August 29. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Task Force Meeting Information, 2002 September 20. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Working Papers and Notes, 2002. (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - DUI Task Force, 2002-2005.
    - Bill Signing Ceremony, 2004. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2002 July-2003 March. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2003 May-July. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2003 August-2004 April. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2004 May-2005 September. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - DUI Initiatives by Principal Matrix, 2004-2005. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, 2003. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Report and Recommendations, 2003. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Gangs, 2003-2005.
    - Anti-Gang Federal Funding Proposals, 2004-2005. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Anti-Gang Task Force and Advisory Committee Joint Session, 2003. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 2004-2005. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Interagency Anti-Gang Workgroup Information, 2005. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Press Conference Material, 2004. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Press Material, 2004-2005. (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Hurricanes and Storms, 2003-2005.
    - Correspondence, 2003-2004. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2004-2005. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Evacuation Plans (Public Safety Agencies), 2003. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Hearing Testimonies, 2003. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Press Material, 2003-2004. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Reports and Summaries, 2003-2005. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports-Dept. of Emergency Management, 2003-2004. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports-Dept. of Emergency Management, 2004. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Narcotics Enforcement, 2003-2005.
    - Statistical Summaries (Virginia State Police), 2003. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Statistical Summaries (Virginia State Police), 2004 January-June. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Statistical Summaries (Virginia State Police), 2004 July-December. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Statistical Summaries (Virginia State Police), 2005. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Sniper Attacks, 2002-2005.
    - Correspondence, 2002 October. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2002 October-December. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2005. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Press Material and Notes, 2002. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Virgina Citizen Soldier Support Council, 2003-2005.
    - Correspondence, 2003-2004. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2004. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2004-2005. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - General Information, 2003-2005. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - General Information, 2003-2005. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - General Information, 2003-2005. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Press Material, 2003-2005. (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Series VII. Legislative Files, 2001-2005., Extent: 9.5 cu. ft. (Box 52-78)
  Contains legislative action summaries, enrolled bill reviews, financial impact statements, and other miscellaneous legislation-related documents which explain in detail various bills brought before and voted upon by both the Senate and the House of Delegates. The Secretary of Public Safety was tapped by the Governor to respond to all General Assembly activity involving the agencies and boards assigned to his office. Decisions were reached with the aid of agency heads with working knowledge of how legislation might affect the agency's ability to operate. Most of the files contain legislative action summaries which include whether the Secretary supported the bill, supported it with amendment, opposed the bill, or took no position on it. The summaries often contain comments and reasons for support or opposition. The files for bills that were not killed in committee or withdrawn also contain enrolled bill reviews, which summarize the bill and the number votes for passage achieved by the House and Senate. The reviews also include notations as to whether the Governor should sign, ask to amend, or to veto the bill. Most files contain a full text version of the bill and any changes that were made to it as it progressed through the General Assembly. Some files contain fiscal impact statements which detail the monetary affect any legislation might have on certain agencies, as well as general agency impact analysis. Others also contain internal correspondence related to that particular bill. Also included in this series are files pertaining to various aspects of the legislation process such as bill tracking, carryover legislation, and legislative proposals. The proposals are submitted in the months prior to the January start of the Legislative Session, so the dates may differ slightly. Proposals for the following year are placed with the later files (e.g., 2005 proposals were written in late 2004, but are kept with the 2005 legislative files). This also applies to material created in late 2001 for use during the 2002 Legislative Session.
  Files are arranged chronologically by year, then by bill number. House bills are first, Senate bills are second, and joint bills are third. Miscellaneous files are arranged alphabetically by title at the end of each year.
  - Legislative Files, 2002.
    - House Bills: HB 3 - HB 25. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 32 - HB 55. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 58 - HB 70. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 95 - HB 119. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 129 - HB 168. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 196 - HB 223. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 224 - HB 249. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 258 - HB 269. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 271 - HB 298. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 300 - HB 308. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 310 - HB 343. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 345 - HB 360. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 362 - HB 370. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 399 - HB 420. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 424 - HB 452. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 453 - HB 472. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 488. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 498 - HB 509. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 511 - HB 527. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 539 - HB 546. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 547 - HB 566. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 581 - HB 604. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 608 - HB 654. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 655 - HB 678. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 700 - HB 711. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 719 - HB 728. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 751 - HB 788. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 789 - HB 807. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 808 - HB 821. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 830 - HB 873. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 874 - HB 893. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 894 - HB 915. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 917 - HB 948. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - House Bills: HB 950 - HB 954. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - House Bills: HB 956 - HB 962. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - House Bills: HB 964 - HB 999. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - House Bills: HB 1000 - HB 1031. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - House Bills: HB 1032 - HB 1059. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - House Bills: HB 1068 - HB 1115. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - House Bills: HB 1117 - HB 1127. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - House Bills: HB 1140 - HB 1152. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - House Bills: HB 1154 - HB 1186. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - House Bills: HB 1193 - HB 1207. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - House Bills: HB 1209 - HB 1224. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - House Bills: HB 1227 - HB 1246. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - House Bills: HB 1251 - HB 1274. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - House Bills: HB 1275 - HB 1301. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - House Bills: HB 1307 - HB 1303. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: HB 1344 - HB 1372. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bills: SB 10 - SB 23. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills: SB 25 - SB 57. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Senate Bills: SB 71 - SB 90. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: SB 97 - SB 128. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 132 - SB 135. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Senate Bills: SB 136 - SB 155. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bills: SB 157 - SB 210. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills: SB 221 - SB 228. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills: SB 252 - SB 273. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bills: SB 280 - SB 90. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills: SB 291 - SB 304. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Senate Bills: SB 305 - SB 318. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Senate Bills: SB 321 - SB 353. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Senate Bills: SB 355 - SB 381. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Senate Bills: SB 394 - SB 410. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bills: SB 418 - SB 424. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills: SB 425 - SB 445. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Senate Bills: SB 452 - SB 474. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: SB 475 - SB 513. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bills: SB 514. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Senate Bills: SB 518 - SB 533. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bills: SB 534 - SB 591. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills: SB 593. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills: SB 605 - SB 635. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bills: SB 641 - SB 642. (Box 56, Folder 14)